B1.
David and Nora are visiting the Natural History Museum.
Listen to them talking to the guide and matching the pictures with the correct information.
That's a funny bird.
I've never seen a bird like that before.
That's a dodo.
They lived on Earth a long time ago.
You mean there aren't any left? That's right.
Oh, that's too bad.
Look at this! Wow!
It's so big!
That's a blue whale.
Are there a lot of blue whales? No.
There are only about 10,000 to 25,000 blue whales around the world.
If we don't stop hunting them, soon there'll be none left. Look!
This is a tiger.
Yes, it's a South China tiger.
There are few left in the world. That's sad.
What about this bird?
This is a bald eagle.
It was once in danger, but not anymore because people have stopped hunting them.